{
    "subject": "resource/Kahlil_Gibran",
    "predicate": "ontology/notableWork",
    "object": "resource/Broken_Wings_(Gibran_novel)",
    "human_readable": "Kahlil Gibran's notable work is 'Broken Wings'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7529973983764648,
            "question": "Name a famous work by Kahlil Gibran."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5821280479431152,
            "question": "Which book is considered one of Kahlil Gibran's most notable works?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4593876004219055,
            "question": "Who wrote 'Broken Wings'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45482930541038513,
            "question": "What is Kahlil Gibran best known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41686782240867615,
            "question": "What genre does 'Broken Wings' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2800138294696808,
            "question": "Kahlil Gibran is renowned for writing which kind of literature?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2583168148994446,
            "question": "What literary work explores themes of love and loss by Kahlil Gibran?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18985363841056824,
            "question": "What is the title of Kahlil Gibran's celebrated novel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12655937671661377,
            "question": "Which novel by Kahlil Gibran deals with the complexities of human relationships?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.02025027573108673,
            "question": "Which book features a story about love, longing, and the pain of separation?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kahlil Gibran's notable work is 'Broken Wings'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8271_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which novel by Kahlil Gibran deals with the complexities of human relationships?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8271_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the title of Kahlil Gibran's celebrated novel?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8271_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What literary work explores themes of love and loss by Kahlil Gibran?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8271_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8271_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8271_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8271_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8271_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8271_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8271_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8271_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8271_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8271_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8271_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information about Kahlil Gibran and his notable works, including \"The Broken Wings,\" which supports the statement that Kahlil Gibran's notable work is \"The Broken Wings.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}